Washingtoniana Slide Collection P026 P026
Test
- Series 5: Chamber of Commerce
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4433)
      View of crowd and Lincoln Memorial (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4434)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4435)
      Coretta Scott King, Walter Fauntroy, Jesse Jackson, Harry Belafonte and other leaders marching with crowd (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4436)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4437)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4438)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4439)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4440)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4441)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4442)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4443)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4444)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4445)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue at 16th Street NW), 1983 August 27 (Item 4446)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue at 16th Street NW), 1983 August 27 (Item 4447)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue at 17th Street NW), 1983 August 27 (Item 4448)
      People standing on platform with crowd marching in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue at 17th Street NW), 1983 August 27 (Item 4449)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4450)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4451)
      Marchers with motorcycle police in foreground (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4452)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4453)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4454)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4455)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4456)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4457)
      Jesse Jackson with male reporter (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4458)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4459)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4460)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4461)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4462)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4463)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4464)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4465)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4466)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4467)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4468)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4469)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4470)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4471)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4472)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4473)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4474)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4475)
      Maya Angelou speaking, surrounded by crowd (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4476)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4477)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4478)
      Martin Luther King, Sr. and grandchildren at podium, surrounded by crowd (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4479)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4480)
      People sitting on ground amidst signs (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4481)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4482)
      People sitting on ground, Washington Monument in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4483)
      People wading through pool, Washington Monument in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4484)
      People carrying banner, "Justice, justice, thou shalt pursue" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4485)
      Man with bullhorn in front of banner, "Throw down in the street, not at the ballot box! Revolution in the 80's - Go fo it! Revolutionary Communist Party" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4486)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4487)
      People standing behind fence with MLK fan and signs (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4488)
      Marchers with banner, "AFSCME in the public service" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4489)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4490)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4491)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4492)
      Marchers carrying signs, Washington Monument in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4493)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4494)
      Jesse Jackson speaking, surrounded by crowd (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4495)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4496)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4497)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4498)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4499)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4500)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4501)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4502)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4503)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4504)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4505)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4506)
      Jesse Jackson and Walter Fauntroy with marchers (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4507)
      Coretta Scott King, Walter Fauntroy, Jesse Jackson, Alan Cranston, Harry Belafonte and other leaders marching with crowd (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4508)
      Marchers carrying signs, motorcycle police in foreground (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4509)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (D Street SW at 12th Street SW), 1983 August 27 (Item 4510)
      Pollution from building (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4511)
      Pollution over mall (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4512)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4513)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4514)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4515)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4516)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4517)
      People with signs, "Service employees international union, we share the dream" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4518)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4519)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4520)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Hoover Building, 1401 Constitution Ave, NW), 1983 August 27 (Item 4521)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Hoover Building, 1401 Constitution Ave, NW), 1983 August 27 (Item 4522)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4523)
      Man seated with sign, "Reagan kiss my [picture of donkey], SEIU" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4524)
      People carrying banner, "Jobs, peace, income now!" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4525)
      Crowd, stage, papers on ground (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4526)
      Garbage truck, people walking, piles of signs (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4527)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4528)
      View of crowd (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4529)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4530)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4531)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4532)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4533)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4534)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4535)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4536)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4537)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4538)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4539)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4540)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4541)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4542)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4543)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4544)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4545)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4546)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4547)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4548)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4549)
      View of crowd on march route, from Washington Monument (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4550)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4551)
      View of crowd from Washington Monument (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4552)
      Group of spectators holding fan with MLK's image (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4553)
      View of crowd and stage from Washington Monument (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4554)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4555)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4556)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4557)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4558)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4559)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4560)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4561)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4562)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4563)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4564)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue at 15th Street NW), 1983 August 27 (Item 4565)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4566)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4567)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4568)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4569)
      Coretta Scott King on stage (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4570)
      Group of marchers carrying banner, "All peoples congress; peoples antiwar mobilization" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4571)
      People under banner, "A clean safe environment…everyone's right" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4572)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4573)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4574)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4575)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4576)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4577)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4578)
      Ruby Dee and Ossie Davis (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4579)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4580)
      People under banner, "Dr. King's way, the people's way, the independent way; coalition for a people's march" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4581)
      Man buying MLK fan from two men and two women (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4582)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4583)
      View of balloons over Capitol; crowd below with banner, "Carpenters District Council" (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4584)
      Young boy walking over pile of UAW signs; crowd in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4585)
      Young boy walking over pile of UAW signs; crowd and Washington Monument in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4586)
      Pile of paper; man taking down banner from stage in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4587)
      People marching and carrying "Machinists Union" signs (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4588)
      Women marching and carrying colorful mural (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4589)
      View from behind of people marching, signs and papers on ground (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4590)
      People marching and carrying signs (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4591)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4592)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4593)
      Man and woman holding banner, "Teamsters Truck Drivers, Union Local 407" (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4594)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4595)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4596)
      Row of marchers in orange shirts, in front of Coretta Scott King, Walter Fauntroy, Jesse Jackson, Harry Belafonte and other leaders (Photographer: David Valdez)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4597)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Constitution Avenue), 1983 August 27 (Item 4598)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4599)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4600)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4601)
      Coretta Scott King speaking, Gloria Steinem to side (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4602)
      Coretta Scott King, Ossie Davis and Gloria Steinem (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4603)
      Crowd, Capitol in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4604)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4605)
      Man holding signs, in shadow against sky (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Washington Monument), 1983 August 27 (Item 4606)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4607)
      Man in suit in pool with overturned umbrella (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4608)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial Reflecting Pool), 1983 August 27 (Item 4609)
      People holding banners, some with legs in pool (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4610)
      People assembling banner, "Kansas City Autoworkers want Jobs, Peace, Freedom"; Capitol and Smithsonian Castle in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4611)
      Stacks of United Auto Workers signs; Capitol in background (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4612)
      View of crowd with signs (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4613)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4614)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4615)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4616)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4617)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4618)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4619)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (Lincoln Memorial), 1983 August 27 (Item 4620)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4621)
      View of mall with scattered papers and signs, from Washington Monument (Photographer: Gary Kieffer)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4622)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4623)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4624)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4625)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4626)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4627)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4628)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4629)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4630)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4631)
    - 20th Anniversary March on Washington (National Mall), 1983 August 27 (Item 4632)